[
  {
    "question": "Translate 'Mulher' to english.",
    "choice1": "Man",
    "choice2": "Woman",
    "choice3": "Dog",
    "choice4": "Ball",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'I'",
    "choice1": "eu",
    "choice2": "ela",
    "choice3": "oi",
    "choice4": "nao",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank '__ sou'      (I am, in english)",
    "choice1": "Oi",
    "choice2": "Tchau",
    "choice3": "Nao",
    "choice4": "Eu",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'am'",
    "choice1": "sou",
    "choice2": "nao",
    "choice3": "sim",
    "choice4": "eu",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Say 'I am a man'",
    "choice1": "Eu sou um homem",
    "choice2": "Eu sou uma mulher",
    "choice3": "Eu sou um carro",
    "choice4": "Eu sou um gato",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Translate 'Mulher' to english.",
    "choice1": "Man",
    "choice2": "Woman",
    "choice3": "Dog",
    "choice4": "Ball",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'I'",
    "choice1": "eu",
    "choice2": "ela",
    "choice3": "oi",
    "choice4": "nao",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank '__ sou'      (I am, in english)",
    "choice1": "Oi",
    "choice2": "Tchau",
    "choice3": "Nao",
    "choice4": "Eu",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you say 'am'",
    "choice1": "sou",
    "choice2": "nao",
    "choice3": "sim",
    "choice4": "eu",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Say 'I am a man'",
    "choice1": "Eu sou um homem",
    "choice2": "Eu sou uma mulher",
    "choice3": "Eu sou um carro",
    "choice4": "Eu sou um gato",
    "answer": 1
  }
]
